[
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are happy. Sterpus is impus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are happy. Shumpus is numpus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Sam is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Sam is impus. Impuses are happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are discordant. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are discordant. Impus is rompus. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are numpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Grimpus is lorpus. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Gorpus is impus. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are spicy. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are spicy. Dumpus is grimpus. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is wooden. Impus is jompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is wooden. Gorpus is shumpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impus is jompus. Stella is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are metallic. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are metallic. Tumpus is rompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are cold. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are cold. Sterpus is yumpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Vumpus is jompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are fruity. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are fruity. Gorpus is lorpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Vumpus is brimpus. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is impus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is impus. Impuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are opaque. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are opaque. Impus is dumpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are slow. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are slow. Jompus is lempus. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is amenable. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is amenable. Dumpus is lempus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are moderate. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are moderate. Dumpus is lorpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpus is sweet. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpus is sweet. Impus is jompus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impus is fast. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impus is fast. Brimpus is lorpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impus is fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are transparent. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are transparent. Wumpus is rompus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are dull. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are dull. Brimpus is grimpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is yumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Brimpus is lorpus. Alex is yumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are small. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are small. Tumpus is gorpus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Lempus is sterpus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpus is earthy. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpus is earthy. Brimpus is zumpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are numpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Gorpus is wumpus. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are fruity. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are fruity. Tumpus is gorpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompuses are brown. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is lorpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are brown. Yumpus is wumpus. Sam is lorpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Yumpus is zumpus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Zumpus is gorpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is muffled. Impus is yumpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is impus. Impus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is muffled. Zumpus is sterpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is impus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is impus. Impus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is impus. Impus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is impus. Impus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are small. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are small. Yumpus is vumpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is large. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is impus. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is large. Yumpus is sterpus. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is impus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is impus. Impuses are rompuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is impus. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is impus. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is rompus. Rompus is large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompuses are transparent. Impus is rompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is rompus. Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are transparent. Wumpus is brimpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impus is rompus. Stella is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impus is rompus. Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impus is transparent. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impus is transparent. Dumpus is yumpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impus is transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Tumpus is lempus. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are floral. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are floral. Jompus is zumpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are cold. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are cold. Gorpus is sterpus. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are slow. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is lorpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are slow. Tumpus is sterpus. Alex is lorpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Lempus is numpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Vumpus is shumpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is lempus. Lempus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Alex is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is snowy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Zumpus is tumpus. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is snowy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are bitter. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are bitter. Shumpus is sterpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are bitter. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are bitter. Zumpus is numpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Brimpus is gorpus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is cold. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is cold. Lorpus is dumpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are luminous. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are luminous. Tumpus is zumpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempus is hot. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempus is hot. Numpus is gorpus. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are transparent. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are transparent. Rompus is brimpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are dull. Brimpus is impus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is impus. Stella is impus. Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are dull. Vumpus is lempus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is impus. Stella is impus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is impus. Stella is impus. Impuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impus is fruity. Shumpus is impus. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is impus. Polly is impus. Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impus is fruity. Lempus is zumpus. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is impus. Polly is impus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is impus. Polly is impus. Impus is fruity."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are overcast. Impus is dumpus. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is impus. Impus is dumpus. Sally is dumpus. Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are overcast. Rompus is zumpus. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is impus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is impus. Impus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is impus. Impus is dumpus. Sally is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is impus. Impus is dumpus. Sally is dumpus. Dumpuses are overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are fast. Impus is sterpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is impus. Impus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are fast. Fae is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are fast. Lorpus is tumpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is impus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is impus. Impus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is impus. Impus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is impus. Impus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are small. Dumpus is gorpus. Wren is dumpus. True or false: Wren is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus. Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are small. Wren is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are small. Yumpus is shumpus. Wren is dumpus. True or false: Wren is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus. Wren is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus. Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Jompus is grimpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is jompus. Jompus is grimpus. Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Fae is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Lempus is yumpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is jompus. Jompus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is jompus. Jompus is grimpus. Fae is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is jompus. Jompus is grimpus. Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are earthy. Gorpus is wumpus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are earthy. Sam is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are earthy. Brimpus is yumpus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are sour. Numpus is wumpus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sour. Sam is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are sour. Dumpus is jompus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Dumpus is gorpus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Fae is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Lorpus is jompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpuses are rainy. Vumpus is zumpus. Max is vumpus. True or false: Max is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is zumpus. Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are rainy. Max is rainy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpuses are rainy. Dumpus is lorpus. Max is vumpus. True or false: Max is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is zumpus. Max is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is zumpus. Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are rainy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are sweet. Impus is gorpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is gorpus. Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are sweet. Stella is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are sweet. Tumpus is numpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impus is gorpus. Stella is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impus is gorpus. Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is blue. Zumpuses are yumpuses. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is blue. Fae is blue. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is blue. Rompus is tumpus. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is blue."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is brown. Numpus is vumpus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is brown. Sam is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is brown. Brimpus is rompus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Max is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Lempus is numpus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are cold. Brimpus is lempus. Sally is brimpus. True or false: Sally is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is brimpus. Brimpus is lempus. Sally is lempus. Lempuses are cold. Sally is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are cold. Grimpus is gorpus. Sally is brimpus. True or false: Sally is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is brimpus. Brimpus is lempus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is brimpus. Brimpus is lempus. Sally is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is brimpus. Brimpus is lempus. Sally is lempus. Lempuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are sunny. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are sunny. Max is sunny. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are sunny. Shumpus is tumpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Max is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are sunny."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are amenable. Impus is shumpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is shumpus. Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are amenable. Stella is amenable. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are amenable. Lorpus is yumpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impus is shumpus. Stella is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impus is shumpus. Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are amenable."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are moderate. Dumpuses are lempuses. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are lempuses. Stella is lempus. Lempuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are moderate. Wumpus is tumpus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are lempuses. Stella is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are lempuses. Stella is lempus. Lempuses are moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are large. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is jompus. Jompuses are large. Fae is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are large. Tumpus is zumpus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is jompus. Jompuses are large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is temperate. Numpus is sterpus. Fae is numpus. True or false: Fae is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is numpus. Numpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpus is temperate. Fae is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is temperate. Wumpus is grimpus. Fae is numpus. True or false: Fae is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is numpus. Numpus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is numpus. Numpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is numpus. Numpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpus is temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are aggressive. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is numpus. True or false: Sally is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are aggressive. Sally is aggressive. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are aggressive. Sterpus is shumpus. Sally is numpus. True or false: Sally is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are aggressive."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are liquid. Brimpuses are shumpuses. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are shumpuses. Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are liquid. Stella is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are liquid. Grimpus is rompus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are shumpuses. Stella is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are shumpuses. Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are muffled. Impuses are vumpuses. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is impus. Impuses are vumpuses. Wren is vumpus. Vumpuses are muffled. Wren is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are muffled. Tumpus is sterpus. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is impus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is impus. Impuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is impus. Impuses are vumpuses. Wren is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is impus. Impuses are vumpuses. Wren is vumpus. Vumpuses are muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are loud. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is jompus. True or false: Rex is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are loud. Rex is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are loud. Tumpus is wumpus. Rex is jompus. True or false: Rex is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is nervous. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is dumpus. True or false: Polly is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is jompus. Jompus is nervous. Polly is nervous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is nervous. Grimpus is gorpus. Polly is dumpus. True or false: Polly is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is jompus. Jompus is nervous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is feisty. Impus is tumpus. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is impus. Impus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is feisty. Alex is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is feisty. Lorpus is sterpus. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is impus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is impus. Impus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is impus. Impus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is impus. Impus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is fast. Rompus is dumpus. Max is rompus. True or false: Max is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is rompus. Rompus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is fast. Max is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is fast. Gorpus is jompus. Max is rompus. True or false: Max is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is rompus. Rompus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is rompus. Rompus is dumpus. Max is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is rompus. Rompus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is windy. Tumpus is grimpus. Max is tumpus. True or false: Max is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus. Max is grimpus. Grimpus is windy. Max is windy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is windy. Lempus is rompus. Max is tumpus. True or false: Max is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus. Max is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus. Max is grimpus. Grimpus is windy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are kind. Shumpus is jompus. Sam is shumpus. True or false: Sam is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are kind. Sam is kind. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are kind. Brimpus is sterpus. Sam is shumpus. True or false: Sam is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus. Sam is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are kind."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Vumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Alex is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Brimpus is grimpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are sweet. Vumpus is wumpus. Sally is vumpus. True or false: Sally is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus. Sally is wumpus. Wumpuses are sweet. Sally is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are sweet. Lorpus is brimpus. Sally is vumpus. True or false: Sally is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus. Sally is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus. Sally is wumpus. Wumpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is moderate. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is moderate. Alex is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is moderate. Lempus is jompus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are discordant. Grimpus is dumpus. Rex is grimpus. True or false: Rex is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpus is dumpus. Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are discordant. Rex is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are discordant. Tumpus is wumpus. Rex is grimpus. True or false: Rex is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpus is dumpus. Rex is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpus is dumpus. Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are small. Vumpuses are impuses. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impuses are small. Rex is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are small. Numpus is wumpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are luminous. Numpuses are jompuses. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are luminous. Rex is luminous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are luminous. Sterpus is brimpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are luminous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are luminous. Gorpuses are yumpuses. Fae is gorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are luminous. Lorpus is tumpus. Fae is gorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are luminous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are red. Jompuses are sterpuses. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpuses are red. Sam is red. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are red. Dumpus is numpus. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpuses are red."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is kind. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is numpus. True or false: Sally is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is kind. Sally is kind. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is kind. Lempus is impus. Sally is numpus. True or false: Sally is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is kind."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impus is muffled. Zumpus is impus. Sally is zumpus. True or false: Sally is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus. Sally is impus. Impus is muffled. Sally is muffled. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Impus is muffled. Brimpus is lorpus. Sally is zumpus. True or false: Sally is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus. Sally is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus. Sally is impus. Impus is muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are aggressive. Impuses are lempuses. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is impus. Impuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempuses are aggressive. Wren is aggressive. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are aggressive. Brimpus is yumpus. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is impus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is impus. Impuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is impus. Impuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is impus. Impuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempuses are aggressive."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is loud. Gorpuses are rompuses. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are rompuses. Stella is rompus. Rompus is loud. Stella is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is loud. Impus is dumpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are rompuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are rompuses. Stella is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are rompuses. Stella is rompus. Rompus is loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are fast. Jompuses are numpuses. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses. Stella is numpus. Numpuses are fast. Stella is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are fast. Zumpus is grimpus. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses. Stella is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses. Stella is numpus. Numpuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are large. Tumpus is shumpus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are large. Alex is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are large. Impus is grimpus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is sour. Vumpus is jompus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Sam is jompus. Jompus is sour. Sam is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is sour. Lorpus is gorpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Sam is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Sam is jompus. Jompus is sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpus is dull. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is vumpus. True or false: Sally is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is dull. Sally is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpus is dull. Zumpus is lempus. Sally is vumpus. True or false: Sally is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are liquid. Numpuses are yumpuses. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are liquid. Alex is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are liquid. Tumpus is shumpus. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are large. Lempus is yumpus. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lempus. Lempus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are large. Fae is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are large. Gorpus is wumpus. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lempus. Lempus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lempus. Lempus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lempus. Lempus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is nervous. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is jompus. True or false: Rex is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is nervous. Rex is nervous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is nervous. Lorpus is rompus. Rex is jompus. True or false: Rex is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is nervous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are slow. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are slow. Stella is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are slow. Dumpus is rompus. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is angry. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is angry. Alex is angry. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is angry. Jompus is yumpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is angry."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is bitter. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Polly is wumpus. True or false: Polly is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Polly is grimpus. Grimpus is bitter. Polly is bitter. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is bitter. Zumpus is gorpus. Polly is wumpus. True or false: Polly is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Polly is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Polly is grimpus. Grimpus is bitter."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is transparent. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is jompus. Jompus is transparent. Fae is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is transparent. Rompus is tumpus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is jompus. Fae is jompus. Jompus is transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is mean. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpus is mean. Wren is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is mean. Gorpus is yumpus. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpus is mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are orange. Lempus is jompus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompuses are orange. Stella is orange. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are orange. Impus is lorpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus. Stella is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompuses are orange."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are aggressive. Brimpuses are lempuses. Wren is brimpus. True or false: Wren is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempuses are aggressive. Wren is aggressive. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are aggressive. Wumpus is rompus. Wren is brimpus. True or false: Wren is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempuses are aggressive."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are blue. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is lempus. True or false: Sam is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are blue. Sam is blue. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are blue. Shumpus is dumpus. Sam is lempus. True or false: Sam is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are blue."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are spicy. Rompus is wumpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are spicy. Stella is spicy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are spicy. Dumpus is brimpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are spicy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompuses are dull. Grimpus is rompus. Sally is grimpus. True or false: Sally is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is rompus. Sally is rompus. Rompuses are dull. Sally is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are dull. Dumpus is gorpus. Sally is grimpus. True or false: Sally is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is rompus. Sally is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is rompus. Sally is rompus. Rompuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impus is muffled. Wumpus is impus. Alex is wumpus. True or false: Alex is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpus is impus. Alex is impus. Impus is muffled. Alex is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impus is muffled. Tumpus is shumpus. Alex is wumpus. True or false: Alex is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpus is impus. Alex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpus is impus. Alex is impus. Impus is muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are orange. Zumpus is tumpus. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is tumpus. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are orange. Sam is orange. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are orange. Lorpus is sterpus. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is tumpus. Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is tumpus. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are orange."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is bright. Zumpus is shumpus. Wren is zumpus. True or false: Wren is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpus is shumpus. Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is bright. Wren is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is bright. Rompus is jompus. Wren is zumpus. True or false: Wren is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpus is shumpus. Wren is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpus is shumpus. Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is yumpus. True or false: Sally is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Sally is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Numpus is jompus. Sally is yumpus. True or false: Sally is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpuses are opaque. Grimpus is zumpus. Max is grimpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is grimpus. Grimpus is zumpus. Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are opaque. Max is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpuses are opaque. Lempus is wumpus. Max is grimpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is grimpus. Grimpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is grimpus. Grimpus is zumpus. Max is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is grimpus. Grimpus is zumpus. Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are brown. Tumpuses are lempuses. Sally is tumpus. True or false: Sally is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are lempuses. Sally is lempus. Lempuses are brown. Sally is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are brown. Vumpus is grimpus. Sally is tumpus. True or false: Sally is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are lempuses. Sally is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are lempuses. Sally is lempus. Lempuses are brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are slow. Brimpus is tumpus. Sam is brimpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is tumpus. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are slow. Sam is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are slow. Dumpus is vumpus. Sam is brimpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is tumpus. Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is tumpus. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are wooden. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are wooden. Sam is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are wooden. Lempus is tumpus. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is floral. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Polly is grimpus. True or false: Polly is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is floral. Polly is floral. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is floral. Lempus is wumpus. Polly is grimpus. True or false: Polly is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is floral."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are loud. Vumpus is impus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is impus. Fae is impus. Impuses are loud. Fae is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are loud. Lorpus is grimpus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is impus. Fae is impus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is impus. Fae is impus. Impuses are loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are sweet. Sterpus is jompus. Polly is sterpus. True or false: Polly is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are sweet. Polly is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are sweet. Lempus is vumpus. Polly is sterpus. True or false: Polly is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus. Polly is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are dull. Impuses are lempuses. Rex is impus. True or false: Rex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is impus. Impuses are lempuses. Rex is lempus. Lempuses are dull. Rex is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are dull. Brimpus is yumpus. Rex is impus. True or false: Rex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is impus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is impus. Impuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is impus. Impuses are lempuses. Rex is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is impus. Impuses are lempuses. Rex is lempus. Lempuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Brimpus is jompus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Stella is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Lempus is numpus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is jompus. Stella is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are luminous. Shumpus is vumpus. Fae is shumpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are luminous. Grimpus is wumpus. Fae is shumpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are luminous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are mean. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpuses are mean. Sam is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are mean. Brimpus is tumpus. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpuses are mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is small. Dumpus is rompus. Sally is dumpus. True or false: Sally is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is rompus. Sally is rompus. Rompus is small. Sally is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is small. Grimpus is zumpus. Sally is dumpus. True or false: Sally is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is rompus. Sally is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is rompus. Sally is rompus. Rompus is small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is liquid. Vumpuses are sterpuses. Stella is vumpus. True or false: Stella is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are sterpuses. Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is liquid. Stella is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is liquid. Impus is numpus. Stella is vumpus. True or false: Stella is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are sterpuses. Stella is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are sterpuses. Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Max is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Gorpus is yumpus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is slow. Brimpuses are jompuses. Max is brimpus. True or false: Max is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompus is slow. Max is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is slow. Gorpus is lempus. Max is brimpus. True or false: Max is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses. Max is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompus is slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is dull. Lorpus is vumpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is dull. Fae is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is dull. Grimpus is brimpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are dull. Numpuses are sterpuses. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus. Sterpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are dull. Shumpus is jompus. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus. Sterpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are angry. Grimpuses are jompuses. Sam is grimpus. True or false: Sam is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are angry. Sam is angry. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are angry. Numpus is rompus. Sam is grimpus. True or false: Sam is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are angry."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is sunny. Impuses are grimpuses. Max is impus. True or false: Max is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is impus. Impuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpus is sunny. Max is sunny. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is sunny. Numpus is rompus. Max is impus. True or false: Max is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is impus.",
        "response_2": "Max is impus. Impuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is impus. Impuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is impus. Impuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpus is sunny."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are mean. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is jompus. True or false: Alex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impuses are mean. Alex is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are mean. Sterpus is grimpus. Alex is jompus. True or false: Alex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impuses are mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is dull. Yumpuses are shumpuses. Max is yumpus. True or false: Max is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are shumpuses. Max is shumpus. Shumpus is dull. Max is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is dull. Numpus is gorpus. Max is yumpus. True or false: Max is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are shumpuses. Max is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are shumpuses. Max is shumpus. Shumpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are hot. Tumpus is gorpus. Wren is tumpus. True or false: Wren is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpus is gorpus. Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are hot. Wren is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are hot. Dumpus is brimpus. Wren is tumpus. True or false: Wren is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpus is gorpus. Wren is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpus is gorpus. Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are opaque. Impus is lempus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is lempus. Stella is lempus. Lempuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are opaque. Dumpus is wumpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impus is lempus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impus is lempus. Stella is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impus is lempus. Stella is lempus. Lempuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are amenable. Lempuses are wumpuses. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are amenable. Fae is amenable. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are amenable. Zumpus is yumpus. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are amenable."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are hot. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is gorpus. Gorpuses are hot. Rex is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are hot. Yumpus is grimpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is gorpus. Gorpuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is dull. Grimpuses are jompuses. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Wren is jompus. Jompus is dull. Wren is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is dull. Brimpus is lempus. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Wren is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Wren is jompus. Jompus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are bitter. Shumpuses are vumpuses. Sally is shumpus. True or false: Sally is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are bitter. Wumpus is dumpus. Sally is shumpus. True or false: Sally is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are bitter."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are hot. Lorpus is sterpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are hot. Fae is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are hot. Numpus is rompus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpus is temperate. Jompus is zumpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompus is zumpus. Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is temperate. Sally is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpus is temperate. Impus is dumpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is jompus. Jompus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is jompus. Jompus is zumpus. Sally is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is jompus. Jompus is zumpus. Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are earthy. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are earthy. Dumpus is shumpus. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is sour. Dumpuses are tumpuses. Max is dumpus. True or false: Max is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are tumpuses. Max is tumpus. Tumpus is sour. Max is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is sour. Rompus is impus. Max is dumpus. True or false: Max is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are tumpuses. Max is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are tumpuses. Max is tumpus. Tumpus is sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are fast. Yumpuses are wumpuses. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are fast. Fae is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are fast. Jompus is gorpus. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is brown. Shumpus is rompus. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is rompus. Wren is rompus. Rompus is brown. Wren is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is brown. Lorpus is brimpus. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is rompus. Wren is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is rompus. Wren is rompus. Rompus is brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Rex is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Brimpus is wumpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is feisty. Lempus is dumpus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lempus. Lempus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is feisty. Max is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is feisty. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lempus. Lempus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is lempus. Lempus is dumpus. Max is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lempus. Lempus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are moderate. Grimpuses are jompuses. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are moderate. Alex is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are moderate. Sterpus is wumpus. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are fast. Rompuses are tumpuses. Sally is rompus. True or false: Sally is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are fast. Sally is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are fast. Yumpus is shumpus. Sally is rompus. True or false: Sally is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are earthy. Shumpuses are jompuses. Max is shumpus. True or false: Max is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompuses are earthy. Max is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are earthy. Rompus is gorpus. Max is shumpus. True or false: Max is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Max is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Max is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompuses are earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is shy. Rompuses are shumpuses. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses. Sam is shumpus. Shumpus is shy. Sam is shy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is shy. Tumpus is lorpus. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses. Sam is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses. Sam is shumpus. Shumpus is shy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Jompus is yumpus. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is yumpus. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Polly is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Gorpus is dumpus. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is yumpus. Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is yumpus. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are small. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are small. Fae is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are small. Numpus is brimpus. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is impus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is transparent. Jompuses are dumpuses. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are dumpuses. Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is transparent. Fae is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is transparent. Shumpus is tumpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are dumpuses. Fae is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are dumpuses. Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are floral. Rompus is wumpus. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are floral. Sam is floral. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are floral. Shumpus is impus. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is rompus. Rompus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are floral."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are dull. Impuses are tumpuses. Sam is impus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is impus. Impuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are dull. Rompus is shumpus. Sam is impus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is impus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is impus. Impuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is impus. Impuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is impus. Impuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are hot. Tumpus is impus. Stella is tumpus. True or false: Stella is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpus is impus. Stella is impus. Impuses are hot. Stella is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are hot. Numpus is wumpus. Stella is tumpus. True or false: Stella is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpus is impus. Stella is impus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpus is impus. Stella is impus. Impuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are discordant. Impuses are tumpuses. Max is impus. True or false: Max is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is impus. Impuses are tumpuses. Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are discordant. Max is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are discordant. Dumpus is wumpus. Max is impus. True or false: Max is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is impus.",
        "response_2": "Max is impus. Impuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is impus. Impuses are tumpuses. Max is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is impus. Impuses are tumpuses. Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are metallic. Yumpus is wumpus. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is wumpus. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are metallic. Tumpus is vumpus. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is wumpus. Fae is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is wumpus. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are metallic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are sour. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Polly is brimpus. True or false: Polly is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are sour. Polly is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are sour. Shumpus is zumpus. Polly is brimpus. True or false: Polly is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Polly is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpus is fruity. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is fruity. Stella is fruity. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpus is fruity. Impus is numpus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is fruity."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are overcast. Yumpuses are impuses. Sally is yumpus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses. Sally is impus. Impuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are overcast. Sterpus is numpus. Sally is yumpus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses. Sally is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses. Sally is impus. Impuses are overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpus is orange. Jompuses are wumpuses. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are wumpuses. Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is orange. Stella is orange. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpus is orange. Zumpus is brimpus. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are wumpuses. Stella is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is jompus. Jompuses are wumpuses. Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is orange."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impus is transparent. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impus is transparent. Sam is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impus is transparent. Shumpus is vumpus. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impus is transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are opaque. Numpuses are impuses. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are opaque. Sam is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are opaque. Dumpus is vumpus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are impuses. Sam is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is large. Impus is vumpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is impus. Impus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is large. Fae is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is large. Gorpus is tumpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is impus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is impus. Impus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is impus. Impus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is impus. Impus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are dull. Zumpus is wumpus. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpus is wumpus. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are dull. Fae is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are dull. Grimpus is tumpus. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpus is wumpus. Fae is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpus is wumpus. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is overcast. Lempus is jompus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompus is overcast. Stella is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is overcast. Yumpus is lorpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus. Stella is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompus is overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are transparent. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is dumpus. True or false: Polly is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are transparent. Polly is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are transparent. Yumpus is lorpus. Polly is dumpus. True or false: Polly is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are kind. Vumpus is wumpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are kind. Alex is kind. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are kind. Gorpus is sterpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are kind."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are moderate. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is wumpus. True or false: Fae is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are moderate. Fae is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are moderate. Zumpus is gorpus. Fae is wumpus. True or false: Fae is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is metallic. Zumpuses are tumpuses. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is metallic. Sam is metallic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is metallic. Lempus is dumpus. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is metallic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are small. Dumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are small. Stella is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are small. Lempus is lorpus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is wooden. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Sam is brimpus. True or false: Sam is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpus is wooden. Sam is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is wooden. Gorpus is yumpus. Sam is brimpus. True or false: Sam is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpus is wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Max is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Yumpus is gorpus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Max is jompus. Jompuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are brown. Lorpuses are sterpuses. Max is lorpus. True or false: Max is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are brown. Max is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are brown. Wumpus is impus. Max is lorpus. True or false: Max is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is muffled. Impus is sterpus. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is impus. Impus is sterpus. Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is muffled. Sally is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is muffled. Jompus is lempus. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is impus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is impus. Impus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is impus. Impus is sterpus. Sally is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is impus. Impus is sterpus. Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is snowy. Tumpus is sterpus. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is snowy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is sterpus. Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is snowy. Rex is snowy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is snowy. Grimpus is impus. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is snowy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is sterpus. Rex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is sterpus. Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is snowy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is temperate. Lempuses are shumpuses. Polly is lempus. True or false: Polly is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is temperate. Polly is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is temperate. Vumpus is zumpus. Polly is lempus. True or false: Polly is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpus is hot. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is hot. Rex is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpus is hot. Rompus is dumpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is gorpus. Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is sour. Tumpuses are yumpuses. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus. Yumpus is sour. Alex is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is sour. Shumpus is vumpus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus. Yumpus is sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are red. Gorpuses are vumpuses. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are vumpuses. Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are red. Sam is red. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are red. Lorpus is lempus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are vumpuses. Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are vumpuses. Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are red."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are opaque. Numpuses are lempuses. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempuses are opaque. Wren is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are opaque. Shumpus is zumpus. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are muffled. Zumpuses are impuses. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are muffled. Sam is muffled. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are muffled. Brimpus is vumpus. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are muffled. Tumpus is jompus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is jompus. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are muffled. Alex is muffled. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are muffled. Impus is gorpus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is jompus. Alex is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is jompus. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are happy. Jompuses are numpuses. Wren is jompus. True or false: Wren is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are happy. Wren is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are happy. Vumpus is impus. Wren is jompus. True or false: Wren is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are discordant. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Wren is tumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are discordant. Rompus is brimpus. Wren is tumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Wren is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is slow. Numpuses are shumpuses. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is slow. Alex is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is slow. Wumpus is vumpus. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is nervous. Dumpus is vumpus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is nervous. Sam is nervous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is nervous. Rompus is yumpus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus. Vumpus is nervous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are cold. Lempuses are numpuses. Rex is lempus. True or false: Rex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses. Rex is numpus. Numpuses are cold. Rex is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are cold. Rompus is dumpus. Rex is lempus. True or false: Rex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses. Rex is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses. Rex is numpus. Numpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are discordant. Numpuses are wumpuses. Max is numpus. True or false: Max is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are discordant. Max is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are discordant. Zumpus is gorpus. Max is numpus. True or false: Max is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is sweet. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is sweet. Rex is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is sweet. Impus is yumpus. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is large. Rompuses are sterpuses. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses. Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is large. Stella is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is large. Zumpus is gorpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses. Stella is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses. Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are dull. Sterpuses are wumpuses. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are dull. Max is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are dull. Impus is dumpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is opaque. Tumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is tumpus. True or false: Sally is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is opaque. Sally is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is opaque. Lorpus is sterpus. Sally is tumpus. True or false: Sally is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are mean. Shumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is shumpus. True or false: Fae is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are mean. Fae is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are mean. Jompus is grimpus. Fae is shumpus. True or false: Fae is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are bright. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are bright. Rex is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are bright. Jompus is yumpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Rex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are floral. Vumpus is tumpus. Sally is vumpus. True or false: Sally is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is tumpus. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are floral. Sally is floral. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are floral. Lempus is grimpus. Sally is vumpus. True or false: Sally is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is tumpus. Sally is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is vumpus. Vumpus is tumpus. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are floral."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are muffled. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are muffled. Fae is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are muffled. Wumpus is yumpus. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is impus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is small. Lorpus is dumpus. Wren is lorpus. True or false: Wren is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is dumpus. Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is small. Wren is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is small. Rompus is gorpus. Wren is lorpus. True or false: Wren is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is dumpus. Wren is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is dumpus. Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is small. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Wren is brimpus. True or false: Wren is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is small. Wren is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is small. Numpus is gorpus. Wren is brimpus. True or false: Wren is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Wren is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are hot. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is lorpus. Lorpuses are hot. Polly is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are hot. Numpus is grimpus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is lorpus. Lorpuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is windy. Lorpus is shumpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is shumpus. Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is windy. Fae is windy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is windy. Grimpus is numpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is shumpus. Fae is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is shumpus. Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is windy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is mean. Lempuses are jompuses. Sally is lempus. True or false: Sally is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Sally is jompus. Jompus is mean. Sally is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is mean. Lorpus is gorpus. Sally is lempus. True or false: Sally is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Sally is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are jompuses. Sally is jompus. Jompus is mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpuses are aggressive. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus. Zumpuses are aggressive. Stella is aggressive. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpuses are aggressive. Impus is sterpus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus. Zumpuses are aggressive."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are bright. Jompuses are impuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Sally is impus. Impuses are bright. Sally is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are bright. Zumpus is rompus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Sally is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Sally is impus. Impuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are sweet. Vumpus is dumpus. Stella is vumpus. True or false: Stella is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpus is dumpus. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are sweet. Stella is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are sweet. Sterpus is impus. Stella is vumpus. True or false: Stella is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpus is dumpus. Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpus is dumpus. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are fast. Yumpuses are impuses. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses. Stella is impus. Impuses are fast. Stella is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are fast. Brimpus is lorpus. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses. Stella is impus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are impuses. Stella is impus. Impuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are cold. Vumpuses are jompuses. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are cold. Rex is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are cold. Dumpus is lorpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are angry. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Rex is brimpus. True or false: Rex is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are angry. Rex is angry. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are angry. Impus is yumpus. Rex is brimpus. True or false: Rex is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are angry."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempus is hot. Jompuses are lempuses. Wren is jompus. True or false: Wren is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempus is hot. Wren is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempus is hot. Zumpus is vumpus. Wren is jompus. True or false: Wren is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is jompus. Jompuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempus is hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is rainy. Brimpuses are jompuses. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses. Stella is jompus. Jompus is rainy. Stella is rainy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is rainy. Wumpus is numpus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses. Stella is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are jompuses. Stella is jompus. Jompus is rainy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are brown. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is wumpus. True or false: Alex is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brown. Alex is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are brown. Yumpus is shumpus. Alex is wumpus. True or false: Alex is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are orange. Tumpuses are numpuses. Max is tumpus. True or false: Max is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are numpuses. Max is numpus. Numpuses are orange. Max is orange. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are orange. Lorpus is wumpus. Max is tumpus. True or false: Max is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are numpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are numpuses. Max is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are numpuses. Max is numpus. Numpuses are orange."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are cold. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is wumpus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are cold. Alex is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are cold. Sterpus is lempus. Alex is wumpus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are shy. Lorpus is tumpus. Stella is lorpus. True or false: Stella is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is tumpus. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are shy. Stella is shy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are shy. Vumpus is jompus. Stella is lorpus. True or false: Stella is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is tumpus. Stella is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is tumpus. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are shy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Wumpus is yumpus. Max is wumpus. True or false: Max is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus. Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Max is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Sterpus is impus. Max is wumpus. True or false: Max is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus. Max is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus. Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are temperate. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sally is lempus. True or false: Sally is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are temperate. Sally is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are temperate. Dumpus is impus. Sally is lempus. True or false: Sally is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are brown. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Rex is grimpus. True or false: Rex is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are brown. Rex is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are brown. Impus is numpus. Rex is grimpus. True or false: Rex is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are sour. Jompus is tumpus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is jompus. Jompus is tumpus. Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are sour. Max is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are sour. Gorpus is numpus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is jompus. Jompus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is jompus. Jompus is tumpus. Max is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is jompus. Jompus is tumpus. Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are sour. Rompuses are lempuses. Rex is rompus. True or false: Rex is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Rex is lempus. Lempuses are sour. Rex is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are sour. Zumpus is brimpus. Rex is rompus. True or false: Rex is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Rex is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Rex is lempus. Lempuses are sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are windy. Wumpus is yumpus. Fae is wumpus. True or false: Fae is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are windy. Fae is windy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are windy. Jompus is sterpus. Fae is wumpus. True or false: Fae is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is wumpus. Wumpus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are windy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are sour. Shumpus is wumpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are sour. Alex is sour. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are sour. Tumpus is sterpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are metallic. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is brimpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are metallic. Lorpus is vumpus. Fae is brimpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are metallic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is moderate. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is moderate. Sam is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is moderate. Vumpus is rompus. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpus is small. Gorpus is numpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is numpus. Stella is numpus. Numpus is small. Stella is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpus is small. Lempus is sterpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is numpus. Stella is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is numpus. Stella is numpus. Numpus is small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are opaque. Jompuses are sterpuses. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are opaque. Max is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are opaque. Rompus is lempus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are small. Grimpuses are lempuses. Polly is grimpus. True or false: Polly is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are lempuses. Polly is lempus. Lempuses are small. Polly is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are small. Tumpus is yumpus. Polly is grimpus. True or false: Polly is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are lempuses. Polly is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are lempuses. Polly is lempus. Lempuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is dull. Numpus is dumpus. Polly is numpus. True or false: Polly is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is numpus. Numpus is dumpus. Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is dull. Polly is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is dull. Tumpus is lempus. Polly is numpus. True or false: Polly is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is numpus. Numpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is numpus. Numpus is dumpus. Polly is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is numpus. Numpus is dumpus. Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is discordant. Rompuses are sterpuses. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is discordant. Alex is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is discordant. Brimpus is zumpus. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are feisty. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is jompus. True or false: Alex is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impuses are feisty. Alex is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are feisty. Rompus is wumpus. Alex is jompus. True or false: Alex is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impuses are feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are windy. Gorpus is tumpus. Rex is gorpus. True or false: Rex is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is tumpus. Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are windy. Rex is windy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are windy. Rompus is impus. Rex is gorpus. True or false: Rex is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is tumpus. Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is tumpus. Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are windy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are opaque. Yumpus is sterpus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpus is sterpus. Polly is sterpus. Sterpuses are opaque. Polly is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are opaque. Tumpus is zumpus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpus is sterpus. Polly is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpus is sterpus. Polly is sterpus. Sterpuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are bitter. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sam is lempus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are bitter. Lorpus is dumpus. Sam is lempus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are vumpuses. Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are bitter."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpus is blue. Wumpus is zumpus. Stella is wumpus. True or false: Stella is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is blue. Stella is blue. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpus is blue. Jompus is grimpus. Stella is wumpus. True or false: Stella is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus. Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is blue."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is temperate. Lempuses are yumpuses. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus. Yumpus is temperate. Alex is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is temperate. Vumpus is jompus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses. Alex is yumpus. Yumpus is temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are bright. Sterpus is yumpus. Sally is sterpus. True or false: Sally is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus. Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are bright. Sally is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are bright. Brimpus is gorpus. Sally is sterpus. True or false: Sally is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus. Sally is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus. Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is temperate. Dumpuses are rompuses. Wren is dumpus. True or false: Wren is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpuses are rompuses. Wren is rompus. Rompus is temperate. Wren is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is temperate. Zumpus is brimpus. Wren is dumpus. True or false: Wren is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpuses are rompuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpuses are rompuses. Wren is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is dumpus. Dumpuses are rompuses. Wren is rompus. Rompus is temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is muffled. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sally is shumpus. True or false: Sally is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sally is jompus. Jompus is muffled. Sally is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is muffled. Zumpus is tumpus. Sally is shumpus. True or false: Sally is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sally is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sally is jompus. Jompus is muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpus is mean. Wumpus is zumpus. Rex is wumpus. True or false: Rex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus. Rex is zumpus. Zumpus is mean. Rex is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpus is mean. Sterpus is dumpus. Rex is wumpus. True or false: Rex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus. Rex is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is wumpus. Wumpus is zumpus. Rex is zumpus. Zumpus is mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are slow. Rompus is numpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is numpus. Stella is numpus. Numpuses are slow. Stella is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are slow. Gorpus is shumpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is numpus. Stella is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is rompus. Rompus is numpus. Stella is numpus. Numpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are bitter. Lempus is impus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is impus. Stella is impus. Impuses are bitter. Stella is bitter. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are bitter. Vumpus is gorpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is bitter. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is impus. Stella is impus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is impus. Stella is impus. Impuses are bitter."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are hot. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Alex is brimpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpuses are hot. Alex is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are hot. Grimpus is zumpus. Alex is brimpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is opaque. Tumpuses are rompuses. Stella is tumpus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are rompuses. Stella is rompus. Rompus is opaque. Stella is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is opaque. Zumpus is shumpus. Stella is tumpus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are rompuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are rompuses. Stella is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are rompuses. Stella is rompus. Rompus is opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is feisty. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Wren is zumpus. True or false: Wren is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is feisty. Wren is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is feisty. Numpus is impus. Wren is zumpus. True or false: Wren is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Wren is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is zumpus. Zumpuses are dumpuses. Wren is dumpus. Dumpus is feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are shy. Sterpus is yumpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus. Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are shy. Max is shy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are shy. Rompus is shumpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus. Max is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is yumpus. Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are shy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is sour. Impuses are sterpuses. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is sour. Sally is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is sour. Lempus is gorpus. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is impus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is impus. Impuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Sally is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Sally is sterpus. Sterpus is sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpus is cold. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is cold. Rex is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpus is cold. Numpus is shumpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Rex is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempus is fast. Rompuses are lempuses. Wren is rompus. True or false: Wren is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempus is fast. Wren is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempus is fast. Tumpus is impus. Wren is rompus. True or false: Wren is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Wren is lempus. Lempus is fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is transparent. Grimpus is yumpus. Sam is grimpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Sam is yumpus. Yumpus is transparent. Sam is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is transparent. Shumpus is lempus. Sam is grimpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Sam is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Sam is yumpus. Yumpus is transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are sour. Jompuses are tumpuses. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are sour. Fae is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are sour. Numpus is gorpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is brown. Dumpus is shumpus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is shumpus. Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is brown. Fae is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is brown. Yumpus is jompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is shumpus. Fae is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is shumpus. Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are loud. Rompus is shumpus. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are loud. Alex is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are loud. Sterpus is brimpus. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is fruity. Rompuses are grimpuses. Polly is rompus. True or false: Polly is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses. Polly is grimpus. Grimpus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is fruity. Yumpus is dumpus. Polly is rompus. True or false: Polly is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses. Polly is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses. Polly is grimpus. Grimpus is fruity."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are red. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Max is brimpus. True or false: Max is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are red. Max is red. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are red. Tumpus is numpus. Max is brimpus. True or false: Max is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are red."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are temperate. Brimpus is vumpus. Sam is brimpus. True or false: Sam is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are temperate. Sam is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are temperate. Lorpus is gorpus. Sam is brimpus. True or false: Sam is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is brimpus. Brimpus is vumpus. Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are opaque. Gorpus is vumpus. Fae is gorpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are opaque. Fae is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are opaque. Sterpus is grimpus. Fae is gorpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is gorpus. Gorpus is vumpus. Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are discordant. Zumpus is grimpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is grimpus. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are discordant. Max is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are discordant. Tumpus is vumpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is grimpus. Max is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is grimpus. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpus is fast. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is fast. Sam is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpus is fast. Brimpus is zumpus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sam is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are dull. Gorpuses are impuses. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are impuses. Stella is impus. Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are dull. Lempus is vumpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are impuses. Stella is impus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpuses are impuses. Stella is impus. Impuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are overcast. Grimpuses are tumpuses. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are overcast. Stella is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are overcast. Numpus is lempus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpus is overcast. Lempus is gorpus. Sally is lempus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is lempus. Lempus is gorpus. Sally is gorpus. Gorpus is overcast. Sally is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpus is overcast. Vumpus is zumpus. Sally is lempus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is lempus. Lempus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is lempus. Lempus is gorpus. Sally is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is lempus. Lempus is gorpus. Sally is gorpus. Gorpus is overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are nervous. Shumpus is tumpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are nervous. Alex is nervous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are nervous. Yumpus is vumpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are nervous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are feisty. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Sam is shumpus. True or false: Sam is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are feisty. Sam is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are feisty. Zumpus is rompus. Sam is shumpus. True or false: Sam is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are blue. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impuses are blue. Rex is blue. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are blue. Gorpus is numpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impuses are blue."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompuses are orange. Gorpus is rompus. Rex is gorpus. True or false: Rex is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is rompus. Rex is rompus. Rompuses are orange. Rex is orange. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are orange. Brimpus is shumpus. Rex is gorpus. True or false: Rex is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is rompus. Rex is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is gorpus. Gorpus is rompus. Rex is rompus. Rompuses are orange."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpus is temperate. Lorpus is gorpus. Max is lorpus. True or false: Max is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Max is gorpus. Gorpus is temperate. Max is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpus is temperate. Numpus is grimpus. Max is lorpus. True or false: Max is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Max is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Max is gorpus. Gorpus is temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Rompus is numpus. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Lempus is zumpus. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is numpus. Alex is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is rompus. Rompus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompuses are spicy. Tumpus is rompus. Sam is tumpus. True or false: Sam is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is rompus. Sam is rompus. Rompuses are spicy. Sam is spicy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are spicy. Lorpus is brimpus. Sam is tumpus. True or false: Sam is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is rompus. Sam is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is rompus. Sam is rompus. Rompuses are spicy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are floral. Wumpuses are vumpuses. Polly is wumpus. True or false: Polly is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are vumpuses. Polly is vumpus. Vumpuses are floral. Polly is floral. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are floral. Grimpus is numpus. Polly is wumpus. True or false: Polly is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are vumpuses. Polly is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpuses are vumpuses. Polly is vumpus. Vumpuses are floral."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is slow. Jompus is dumpus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is jompus. Jompus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is slow. Max is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is slow. Impus is vumpus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is jompus. Jompus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is jompus. Jompus is dumpus. Max is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is jompus. Jompus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are floral. Lempuses are numpuses. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses. Max is numpus. Numpuses are floral. Max is floral. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are floral. Wumpus is impus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses. Max is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are numpuses. Max is numpus. Numpuses are floral."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is red. Rompuses are dumpuses. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses. Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is red. Sam is red. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is red. Lorpus is shumpus. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses. Sam is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses. Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is red."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are cold. Lempus is numpus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Max is numpus. Numpuses are cold. Max is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are cold. Yumpus is gorpus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lempus. Lempus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Max is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Max is numpus. Numpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is opaque. Numpuses are vumpuses. Max is numpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are vumpuses. Max is vumpus. Vumpus is opaque. Max is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is opaque. Grimpus is dumpus. Max is numpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are vumpuses. Max is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are vumpuses. Max is vumpus. Vumpus is opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are spicy. Grimpuses are impuses. Polly is grimpus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are impuses. Polly is impus. Impuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are spicy. Shumpus is brimpus. Polly is grimpus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are impuses. Polly is impus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are impuses. Polly is impus. Impuses are spicy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are hot. Sterpus is impus. Alex is sterpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Alex is impus. Impuses are hot. Alex is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are hot. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is sterpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Alex is impus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Alex is impus. Impuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is fast. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is yumpus. True or false: Sally is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is fast. Sally is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is fast. Rompus is zumpus. Sally is yumpus. True or false: Sally is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Sally is grimpus. Grimpus is fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are overcast. Numpuses are sterpuses. Polly is numpus. True or false: Polly is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus. Sterpuses are overcast. Polly is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are overcast. Impus is grimpus. Polly is numpus. True or false: Polly is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus. Sterpuses are overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Brimpus is yumpus. Polly is brimpus. True or false: Polly is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpus is yumpus. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Polly is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Zumpus is lorpus. Polly is brimpus. True or false: Polly is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpus is yumpus. Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is brimpus. Brimpus is yumpus. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are temperate. Jompus is shumpus. Alex is jompus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is jompus. Jompus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are temperate. Alex is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are temperate. Vumpus is tumpus. Alex is jompus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is jompus. Jompus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is jompus. Jompus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is jompus. Jompus is shumpus. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpuses are temperate. Numpus is vumpus. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are temperate. Alex is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are temperate. Yumpus is dumpus. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Alex is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is numpus. Numpus is vumpus. Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are feisty. Rompuses are shumpuses. Fae is rompus. True or false: Fae is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses. Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are feisty. Fae is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are feisty. Numpus is lorpus. Fae is rompus. True or false: Fae is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses. Fae is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are shumpuses. Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are fast. Lempuses are wumpuses. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are fast. Wren is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are fast. Brimpus is grimpus. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are dull. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is lorpus. Lorpuses are dull. Polly is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are dull. Grimpus is sterpus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Polly is lorpus. Lorpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are nervous. Shumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is shumpus. True or false: Sally is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is wumpus. Wumpuses are nervous. Sally is nervous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are nervous. Impus is brimpus. Sally is shumpus. True or false: Sally is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is shumpus. Shumpuses are wumpuses. Sally is wumpus. Wumpuses are nervous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is cold. Wumpus is dumpus. Max is wumpus. True or false: Max is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is cold. Max is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is cold. Zumpus is yumpus. Max is wumpus. True or false: Max is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus. Max is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus. Max is dumpus. Dumpus is cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are cold. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Alex is brimpus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are cold. Alex is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are cold. Lorpus is sterpus. Alex is brimpus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is brimpus. Brimpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are liquid. Impuses are wumpuses. Sam is impus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is impus. Impuses are wumpuses. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are liquid. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is impus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is impus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is impus. Impuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is impus. Impuses are wumpuses. Sam is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is impus. Impuses are wumpuses. Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is dull. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is dull. Stella is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is dull. Lempus is numpus. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are slow. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is brimpus. True or false: Fae is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are slow. Fae is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are slow. Shumpus is rompus. Fae is brimpus. True or false: Fae is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are red. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Max is grimpus. True or false: Max is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are red. Max is red. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are red. Numpus is lempus. Max is grimpus. True or false: Max is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are red."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempus is melodic. Zumpus is lempus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lempus. Max is lempus. Lempus is melodic. Max is melodic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempus is melodic. Rompus is tumpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lempus.",
        "response_3": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lempus. Max is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lempus. Max is lempus. Lempus is melodic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is large. Impuses are yumpuses. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is large. Stella is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is large. Grimpus is vumpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are temperate. Vumpuses are impuses. Stella is vumpus. True or false: Stella is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Stella is impus. Impuses are temperate. Stella is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are temperate. Tumpus is shumpus. Stella is vumpus. True or false: Stella is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Stella is impus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Stella is impus. Impuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sam is shumpus. True or false: Sam is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Sam is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Zumpus is brimpus. Sam is shumpus. True or false: Sam is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are bright. Shumpus is numpus. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is numpus. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are bright. Wren is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are bright. Dumpus is impus. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is numpus. Wren is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is numpus. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is slow. Dumpus is yumpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus. Yumpus is slow. Alex is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is slow. Grimpus is tumpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus. Yumpus is slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Gorpuses are dumpuses. Max is gorpus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is gorpus. Gorpuses are dumpuses. Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled. Max is muffled. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Shumpus is grimpus. Max is gorpus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is gorpus. Gorpuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is gorpus. Gorpuses are dumpuses. Max is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is gorpus. Gorpuses are dumpuses. Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are temperate. Tumpus is grimpus. Polly is tumpus. True or false: Polly is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus. Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are temperate. Polly is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are temperate. Rompus is sterpus. Polly is tumpus. True or false: Polly is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus. Polly is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpus is grimpus. Polly is grimpus. Grimpuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is nervous. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Rex is brimpus. True or false: Rex is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Rex is dumpus. Dumpus is nervous. Rex is nervous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is nervous. Grimpus is wumpus. Rex is brimpus. True or false: Rex is nervous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Rex is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are dumpuses. Rex is dumpus. Dumpus is nervous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpus is earthy. Lempus is wumpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is earthy. Stella is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpus is earthy. Gorpus is lorpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is windy. Lempuses are shumpuses. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses. Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is windy. Fae is windy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is windy. Lorpus is wumpus. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses. Fae is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are shumpuses. Fae is shumpus. Shumpus is windy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are wooden. Rompuses are grimpuses. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are wooden. Alex is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are wooden. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is rompus. True or false: Alex is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is rompus. Rompuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are happy. Vumpuses are shumpuses. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are shumpuses. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are happy. Alex is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are happy. Zumpus is numpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are shumpuses. Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are shumpuses. Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are cold. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is lempus. True or false: Sam is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are cold. Sam is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are cold. Grimpus is rompus. Sam is lempus. True or false: Sam is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Sam is tumpus. Tumpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are happy. Zumpuses are shumpuses. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are shumpuses. Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are happy. Sam is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are happy. Grimpus is impus. Sam is zumpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are shumpuses. Sam is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are shumpuses. Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are feisty. Impus is shumpus. Sam is impus. True or false: Sam is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is impus. Impus is shumpus. Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are feisty. Sam is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are feisty. Brimpus is dumpus. Sam is impus. True or false: Sam is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is impus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is impus. Impus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is impus. Impus is shumpus. Sam is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is impus. Impus is shumpus. Sam is shumpus. Shumpuses are feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempus is opaque. Dumpus is lempus. Polly is dumpus. True or false: Polly is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is lempus. Polly is lempus. Lempus is opaque. Polly is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempus is opaque. Vumpus is lorpus. Polly is dumpus. True or false: Polly is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is lempus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is lempus. Polly is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is lempus. Polly is lempus. Lempus is opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are loud. Numpuses are impuses. Max is numpus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are impuses. Max is impus. Impuses are loud. Max is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are loud. Yumpus is vumpus. Max is numpus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are impuses. Max is impus.",
        "response_4": "Max is numpus. Numpuses are impuses. Max is impus. Impuses are loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are orange. Vumpus is numpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are orange. Alex is orange. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are orange. Yumpus is rompus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is orange. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus. Alex is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are orange."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is small. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is small. Stella is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is small. Vumpus is shumpus. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are discordant. Numpuses are sterpuses. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpuses are discordant. Rex is discordant. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are discordant. Zumpus is tumpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is discordant. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpuses are discordant."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is opaque. Dumpus is vumpus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus. Stella is vumpus. Vumpus is opaque. Stella is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is opaque. Rompus is impus. Stella is dumpus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus. Stella is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is dumpus. Dumpus is vumpus. Stella is vumpus. Vumpus is opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impus is earthy. Zumpus is impus. Sally is zumpus. True or false: Sally is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus. Sally is impus. Impus is earthy. Sally is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impus is earthy. Shumpus is yumpus. Sally is zumpus. True or false: Sally is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus. Sally is impus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpus is impus. Sally is impus. Impus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are rainy. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpuses are rainy. Sam is rainy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are rainy. Vumpus is wumpus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Sam is sterpus. Sterpuses are rainy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are dull. Gorpuses are lempuses. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is snowy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are dull. Sam is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are dull. Shumpus is jompus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is snowy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpus is hot. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Max is tumpus. True or false: Max is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpus is hot. Max is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is hot. Numpus is gorpus. Max is tumpus. True or false: Max is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is tumpus. Tumpuses are sterpuses. Max is sterpus. Sterpus is hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are cold. Zumpus is dumpus. Stella is zumpus. True or false: Stella is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is dumpus. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are cold. Stella is cold. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are cold. Rompus is lorpus. Stella is zumpus. True or false: Stella is cold. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is dumpus. Stella is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is zumpus. Zumpus is dumpus. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is wooden. Jompuses are shumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are shumpuses. Sally is shumpus. Shumpus is wooden. Sally is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is wooden. Numpus is grimpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are shumpuses. Sally is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are shumpuses. Sally is shumpus. Shumpus is wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are overcast. Vumpuses are jompuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are overcast. Sam is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are overcast. Grimpus is numpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are jompuses. Sam is jompus. Jompuses are overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are feisty. Lempus is sterpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are feisty. Stella is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are feisty. Dumpus is wumpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lempus. Lempus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is aggressive. Wumpus is jompus. Polly is wumpus. True or false: Polly is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompus is aggressive. Polly is aggressive. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is aggressive. Gorpus is vumpus. Polly is wumpus. True or false: Polly is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is wumpus. Wumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompus is aggressive."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are dull. Zumpuses are sterpuses. Sally is zumpus. True or false: Sally is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpuses are sterpuses. Sally is sterpus. Sterpuses are dull. Sally is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are dull. Gorpus is tumpus. Sally is zumpus. True or false: Sally is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpuses are sterpuses. Sally is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is zumpus. Zumpuses are sterpuses. Sally is sterpus. Sterpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are brown. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are brown. Sally is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are brown. Zumpus is wumpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sally is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sally is yumpus. Yumpuses are brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are kind. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus. Sterpuses are kind. Alex is kind. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are kind. Grimpus is rompus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are sterpuses. Alex is sterpus. Sterpuses are kind."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are slow. Dumpus is sterpus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are slow. Fae is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are slow. Grimpus is jompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpus is sterpus. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are slow. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are slow. Fae is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are slow. Brimpus is tumpus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Fae is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are gorpuses. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are bright. Numpuses are wumpuses. Fae is numpus. True or false: Fae is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are bright. Fae is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are bright. Tumpus is sterpus. Fae is numpus. True or false: Fae is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Fae is wumpus. Wumpuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are large. Lempuses are yumpuses. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are large. Fae is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are large. Vumpus is numpus. Fae is lempus. True or false: Fae is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is lempus. Lempuses are yumpuses. Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are hot. Lorpus is lempus. Rex is lorpus. True or false: Rex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is lorpus. Lorpus is lempus. Rex is lempus. Lempuses are hot. Rex is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are hot. Wumpus is shumpus. Rex is lorpus. True or false: Rex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is lorpus. Lorpus is lempus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is lorpus. Lorpus is lempus. Rex is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is lorpus. Lorpus is lempus. Rex is lempus. Lempuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is earthy. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Wren is tumpus. Tumpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is earthy. Shumpus is lempus. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Wren is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are tumpuses. Wren is tumpus. Tumpus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is sweet. Sterpus is tumpus. Fae is sterpus. True or false: Fae is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus. Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is sweet. Fae is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is sweet. Grimpus is jompus. Fae is sterpus. True or false: Fae is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus. Fae is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus. Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are red. Lempuses are grimpuses. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are red. Stella is red. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are red. Dumpus is numpus. Stella is lempus. True or false: Stella is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are red."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is sour. Vumpus is grimpus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Fae is grimpus. Grimpus is sour. Fae is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is sour. Impus is wumpus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Fae is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Fae is grimpus. Grimpus is sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are dull. Rompuses are impuses. Fae is rompus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are dull. Fae is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are dull. Tumpus is dumpus. Fae is rompus. True or false: Fae is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are impuses. Fae is impus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is rompus. Rompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are happy. Grimpuses are jompuses. Rex is grimpus. True or false: Rex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are happy. Rex is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are happy. Yumpus is dumpus. Rex is grimpus. True or false: Rex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are jompuses. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are luminous. Tumpuses are shumpuses. Polly is tumpus. True or false: Polly is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are luminous. Polly is luminous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are luminous. Sterpus is rompus. Polly is tumpus. True or false: Polly is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpuses are shumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is tumpus. Tumpuses are shumpuses. Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are luminous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompus is floral. Shumpus is jompus. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus. Wren is jompus. Jompus is floral. Wren is floral. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompus is floral. Numpus is grimpus. Wren is shumpus. True or false: Wren is floral. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus. Wren is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is shumpus. Shumpus is jompus. Wren is jompus. Jompus is floral."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpus is blue. Jompuses are tumpuses. Rex is jompus. True or false: Rex is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is blue. Rex is blue. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is blue. Dumpus is numpus. Rex is jompus. True or false: Rex is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is blue."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpus is happy. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sally is dumpus. True or false: Sally is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sally is gorpus. Gorpus is happy. Sally is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpus is happy. Brimpus is shumpus. Sally is dumpus. True or false: Sally is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sally is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpuses are gorpuses. Sally is gorpus. Gorpus is happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is sweet. Wumpus is dumpus. Sally is wumpus. True or false: Sally is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus. Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is sweet. Sally is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is sweet. Sterpus is gorpus. Sally is wumpus. True or false: Sally is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus. Sally is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is dumpus. Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Impuses are feisty. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are feisty. Fae is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Impuses are feisty. Tumpus is zumpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are wooden. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is rompus. True or false: Max is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are wooden. Max is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are wooden. Zumpus is numpus. Max is rompus. True or false: Max is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpuses are wooden. Jompus is shumpus. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is shumpus. Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are wooden. Polly is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are wooden. Numpus is wumpus. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is shumpus. Polly is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is jompus. Jompus is shumpus. Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are liquid. Zumpus is sterpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is sterpus. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are liquid. Max is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are liquid. Yumpus is tumpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is sterpus. Max is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is sterpus. Max is sterpus. Sterpuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpus is dull. Rompuses are dumpuses. Polly is rompus. True or false: Polly is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses. Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is dull. Polly is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpus is dull. Grimpus is tumpus. Polly is rompus. True or false: Polly is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses. Polly is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are dumpuses. Polly is dumpus. Dumpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is dull. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is shumpus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is dull. Stella is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is dull. Rompus is jompus. Stella is shumpus. True or false: Stella is amenable. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are grimpuses. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Numpuses are bright. Vumpus is numpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus. Rex is numpus. Numpuses are bright. Rex is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are bright. Rompus is yumpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus. Rex is numpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is numpus. Rex is numpus. Numpuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zumpuses are large. Sterpus is zumpus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are large. Sam is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Zumpuses are large. Grimpus is jompus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is zumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus. Zumpuses are large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are slow. Zumpuses are lempuses. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are lempuses. Max is lempus. Lempuses are slow. Max is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are slow. Vumpus is lorpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are lempuses. Max is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Max is zumpus. Zumpuses are lempuses. Max is lempus. Lempuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shumpus is angry. Vumpus is shumpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is shumpus. Rex is shumpus. Shumpus is angry. Rex is angry. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Shumpus is angry. Yumpus is numpus. Rex is vumpus. True or false: Rex is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is shumpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is shumpus. Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is shumpus. Rex is shumpus. Shumpus is angry."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are sweet. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is rompus. True or false: Max is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are sweet. Max is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are sweet. Gorpus is yumpus. Max is rompus. True or false: Max is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is rompus. Rompuses are wumpuses. Max is wumpus. Wumpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tumpuses are bright. Sterpus is tumpus. Alex is sterpus. True or false: Alex is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are bright. Alex is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are bright. Gorpus is shumpus. Alex is sterpus. True or false: Alex is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is sterpus. Sterpus is tumpus. Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are liquid. Impus is lempus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is impus. Impus is lempus. Fae is lempus. Lempuses are liquid. Fae is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are liquid. Grimpus is wumpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is impus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is impus. Impus is lempus.",
        "response_3": "Fae is impus. Impus is lempus. Fae is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is impus. Impus is lempus. Fae is lempus. Lempuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are happy. Numpus is wumpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is wumpus. Rex is wumpus. Wumpuses are happy. Rex is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are happy. Gorpus is sterpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is wumpus. Rex is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is wumpus. Rex is wumpus. Wumpuses are happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vumpus is wooden. Impuses are vumpuses. Rex is impus. True or false: Rex is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is impus. Impuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is wooden. Rex is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Vumpus is wooden. Lempus is jompus. Rex is impus. True or false: Rex is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is impus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is impus. Impuses are vumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is impus. Impuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is impus. Impuses are vumpuses. Rex is vumpus. Vumpus is wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpuses are sunny. Impus is grimpus. Rex is impus. True or false: Rex is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is impus. Impus is grimpus. Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are sunny. Rex is sunny. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are sunny. Brimpus is dumpus. Rex is impus. True or false: Rex is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is impus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is impus. Impus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is impus. Impus is grimpus. Rex is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is impus. Impus is grimpus. Rex is grimpus. Grimpuses are sunny."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is kind. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is shumpus. True or false: Stella is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is kind. Stella is kind. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is kind. Wumpus is dumpus. Stella is shumpus. True or false: Stella is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is kind."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Rompuses are yumpuses. Polly is rompus. True or false: Polly is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Polly is slow. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Lempus is grimpus. Polly is rompus. True or false: Polly is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is rompus. Rompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jompuses are happy. Sterpus is jompus. Rex is sterpus. True or false: Rex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are happy. Rex is happy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are happy. Dumpus is grimpus. Rex is sterpus. True or false: Rex is happy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus. Rex is jompus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is sterpus. Sterpus is jompus. Rex is jompus. Jompuses are happy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gorpuses are shy. Sterpus is gorpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is gorpus. Max is gorpus. Gorpuses are shy. Max is shy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are shy. Vumpus is dumpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is shy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is gorpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is gorpus. Max is gorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is gorpus. Max is gorpus. Gorpuses are shy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lempuses are wooden. Numpuses are lempuses. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses. Alex is lempus. Lempuses are wooden. Alex is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are wooden. Gorpus is zumpus. Alex is numpus. True or false: Alex is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses. Alex is lempus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is numpus. Numpuses are lempuses. Alex is lempus. Lempuses are wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Grimpus is dull. Shumpus is grimpus. Stella is shumpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpus is grimpus. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is dull. Stella is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is dull. Numpus is lorpus. Stella is shumpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpus is grimpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpus is grimpus. Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is shumpus. Shumpus is grimpus. Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpus is moderate. Dumpus is yumpus. Sally is dumpus. True or false: Sally is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus. Sally is yumpus. Yumpus is moderate. Sally is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is moderate. Impus is shumpus. Sally is dumpus. True or false: Sally is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus. Sally is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is dumpus. Dumpus is yumpus. Sally is yumpus. Yumpus is moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are bright. Impus is sterpus. Polly is impus. True or false: Polly is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is impus. Impus is sterpus. Polly is sterpus. Sterpuses are bright. Polly is bright. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are bright. Lorpus is wumpus. Polly is impus. True or false: Polly is bright. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is impus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is impus. Impus is sterpus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is impus. Impus is sterpus. Polly is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is impus. Impus is sterpus. Polly is sterpus. Sterpuses are bright."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dumpuses are small. Numpus is dumpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is dumpus. Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are small. Rex is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are small. Brimpus is grimpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is dumpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is dumpus. Rex is dumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is numpus. Numpus is dumpus. Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yumpuses are large. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Rex is yumpus. Yumpuses are large. Rex is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are large. Gorpus is sterpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Rex is yumpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are yumpuses. Rex is yumpus. Yumpuses are large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is feisty. Vumpus is rompus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus. Polly is rompus. Rompus is feisty. Polly is feisty. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is feisty. Tumpus is yumpus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is feisty. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus. Polly is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus. Polly is rompus. Rompus is feisty."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wumpuses are spicy. Rompus is wumpus. Wren is rompus. True or false: Wren is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are spicy. Wren is spicy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are spicy. Jompus is vumpus. Wren is rompus. True or false: Wren is spicy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is rompus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is rompus. Rompus is wumpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Wren is wumpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is rompus. Rompus is wumpus. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are spicy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompuses are dull. Vumpus is rompus. Max is vumpus. True or false: Max is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus. Max is rompus. Rompuses are dull. Max is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are dull. Impus is lempus. Max is vumpus. True or false: Max is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus. Max is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Max is vumpus. Vumpus is rompus. Max is rompus. Rompuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is dumpus. True or false: Rex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Rex is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Jompus is lorpus. Rex is dumpus. True or false: Rex is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Rex is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is earthy. Lempuses are lorpuses. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpus is earthy. Max is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is earthy. Sterpus is numpus. Max is lempus. True or false: Max is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is lempus. Lempuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rompus is overcast. Impus is rompus. Max is impus. True or false: Max is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is impus. Impus is rompus. Max is rompus. Rompus is overcast. Max is overcast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Rompus is overcast. Shumpus is tumpus. Max is impus. True or false: Max is overcast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is impus.",
        "response_2": "Max is impus. Impus is rompus.",
        "response_3": "Max is impus. Impus is rompus. Max is rompus.",
        "response_4": "Max is impus. Impus is rompus. Max is rompus. Rompus is overcast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is loud. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Max is yumpus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpus is loud. Max is loud. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is loud. Jompus is dumpus. Max is yumpus. True or false: Max is loud. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is yumpus. Yumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpus is loud."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpus is red. Yumpus is brimpus. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is red. Stella is red. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpus is red. Lorpus is rompus. Stella is yumpus. True or false: Stella is red. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is yumpus. Yumpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is red."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is blue. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is blue. Alex is blue. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is blue. Zumpus is sterpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is blue. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is blue."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is earthy. Impuses are lorpuses. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is impus. Impuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is earthy. Rompus is grimpus. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is impus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is impus. Impuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is impus. Impuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is impus. Impuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is earthy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are melodic. Yumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are melodic. Polly is melodic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are melodic. Zumpus is tumpus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is yumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are melodic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are dull. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dull. Wren is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are dull. Gorpus is sterpus. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are luminous. Lorpus is brimpus. Wren is lorpus. True or false: Wren is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are luminous. Wren is luminous. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are luminous. Tumpus is rompus. Wren is lorpus. True or false: Wren is luminous. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus. Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are luminous."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are metallic. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are metallic. Polly is metallic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are metallic. Lorpus is sterpus. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is metallic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are metallic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is angry. Tumpus is lorpus. Sam is tumpus. True or false: Sam is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus. Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is angry. Sam is angry. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is angry. Gorpus is impus. Sam is tumpus. True or false: Sam is angry. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus. Sam is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus. Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is angry."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are large. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are large. Wren is large. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are large. Dumpus is numpus. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is large. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are large."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is temperate. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is temperate. Alex is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is temperate. Shumpus is rompus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are cold. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are cold. Rex is cold. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are cold. Zumpus is sterpus. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is sunny. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are cold."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are muffled. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are muffled. Shumpus is rompus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpuses are brimpuses. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are opaque. Vumpuses are lorpuses. Max is vumpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are opaque. Max is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are opaque. Impus is yumpus. Max is vumpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are small. Jompus is brimpus. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are small. Sam is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are small. Lempus is yumpus. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is jompus. Jompus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Sam is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Sam is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is windy. Zumpus is lorpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lorpus. Max is lorpus. Lorpus is windy. Max is windy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is windy. Brimpus is dumpus. Max is zumpus. True or false: Max is windy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lorpus. Max is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is zumpus. Zumpus is lorpus. Max is lorpus. Lorpus is windy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is slow. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is slow. Stella is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is slow. Numpus is jompus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is slow."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are melodic. Vumpuses are brimpuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are brimpuses. Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are melodic. Sam is melodic. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are melodic. Wumpus is gorpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is melodic. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sam is vumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are brimpuses. Sam is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are brimpuses. Sam is brimpus. Brimpuses are melodic."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are wooden. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are wooden. Stella is wooden. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are wooden. Impus is shumpus. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are wooden."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are rainy. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are rainy. Wren is rainy. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are rainy. Wumpus is rompus. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is rainy. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is lempus. Lempuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are rainy."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are dull. Lempus is lorpus. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is lempus. Lempus is lorpus. Wren is lorpus. Lorpuses are dull. Wren is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are dull. Impus is dumpus. Wren is lempus. True or false: Wren is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is lempus. Lempus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is lempus. Lempus is lorpus. Wren is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is lempus. Lempus is lorpus. Wren is lorpus. Lorpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are small. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is lorpus. Lorpuses are small. Alex is small. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are small. Sterpus is gorpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is small. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is lorpus. Lorpuses are small."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are mean. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Rex is lorpus. Lorpuses are mean. Rex is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are mean. Zumpus is sterpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Rex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Rex is lorpus. Lorpuses are mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpus is muffled. Lempus is brimpus. Rex is lempus. True or false: Rex is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is lempus. Lempus is brimpus. Rex is brimpus. Brimpus is muffled. Rex is muffled. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpus is muffled. Zumpus is jompus. Rex is lempus. True or false: Rex is muffled. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is lempus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is lempus. Lempus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is lempus. Lempus is brimpus. Rex is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is lempus. Lempus is brimpus. Rex is brimpus. Brimpus is muffled."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are dull. Gorpuses are brimpuses. Wren is gorpus. True or false: Wren is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dull. Wren is dull. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are dull. Dumpus is lorpus. Wren is gorpus. True or false: Wren is dull. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is gorpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is gorpus. Gorpuses are brimpuses. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are dull. Zumpuses are brimpuses. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are brimpuses. Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are dull. Fae is dull. False",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are dull. Shumpus is rompus. Fae is zumpus. True or false: Fae is wooden. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is zumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are brimpuses. Fae is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is zumpus. Zumpuses are brimpuses. Fae is brimpus. Brimpuses are dull."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are aggressive. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Wren is brimpus. True or false: Wren is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Wren is lorpus. Lorpuses are aggressive. Wren is aggressive. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are aggressive. Sterpus is numpus. Wren is brimpus. True or false: Wren is aggressive. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Wren is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are lorpuses. Wren is lorpus. Lorpuses are aggressive."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are moderate. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is lorpus. Lorpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are moderate. Brimpus is sterpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is lorpus. Stella is lorpus. Lorpuses are moderate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are liquid. Shumpus is lorpus. Max is shumpus. True or false: Max is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are liquid. Max is liquid. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are liquid. Zumpus is lempus. Max is shumpus. True or false: Max is liquid. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Max is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Max is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are liquid."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is transparent. Tumpus is lorpus. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus. Rex is lorpus. Lorpus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is transparent. Numpus is dumpus. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus. Rex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpus is lorpus. Rex is lorpus. Lorpus is transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are brown. Impus is brimpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are brown. Stella is brown. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are brown. Wumpus is gorpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is brown. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is impus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is impus. Impus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is impus. Impus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is impus. Impus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are brown."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are hot. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is lorpus. Lorpuses are hot. Alex is hot. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are hot. Numpus is yumpus. Alex is shumpus. True or false: Alex is hot. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Alex is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Alex is shumpus. Shumpus is lorpus. Alex is lorpus. Lorpuses are hot."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are fast. Numpuses are lorpuses. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are lorpuses. Rex is lorpus. Lorpuses are fast. Rex is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are fast. Wumpus is yumpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is numpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are lorpuses. Rex is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are lorpuses. Rex is lorpus. Lorpuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpus is sour. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is shumpus. True or false: Fae is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is sour. Fae is sour. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpus is sour. Numpus is wumpus. Fae is shumpus. True or false: Fae is sour. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is shumpus. Shumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is sour."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are transparent. Sterpus is brimpus. Stella is sterpus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are transparent. Wumpus is lorpus. Stella is sterpus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is sterpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is sterpus. Sterpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are transparent."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are kind. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Sally is tumpus. True or false: Sally is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Sally is brimpus. Brimpuses are kind. Sally is kind. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are kind. Dumpus is yumpus. Sally is tumpus. True or false: Sally is kind. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Sally is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Sally is brimpus. Brimpuses are kind."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are temperate. Wumpus is lorpus. Sally is wumpus. True or false: Sally is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is lorpus. Sally is lorpus. Lorpuses are temperate. Sally is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are temperate. Yumpus is rompus. Sally is wumpus. True or false: Sally is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Sally is wumpus.",
        "response_2": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is lorpus.",
        "response_3": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is lorpus. Sally is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Sally is wumpus. Wumpus is lorpus. Sally is lorpus. Lorpuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are sweet. Grimpus is brimpus. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is brimpus. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are sweet. Numpus is vumpus. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Wren is grimpus.",
        "response_2": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is brimpus. Wren is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is brimpus. Wren is brimpus. Brimpuses are sweet."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are temperate. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are temperate. Polly is temperate. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are temperate. Vumpus is rompus. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is temperate. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Polly is shumpus.",
        "response_2": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpuses are brimpuses. Polly is brimpus. Brimpuses are temperate."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are mean. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are mean. Rex is mean. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are mean. Sterpus is shumpus. Rex is tumpus. True or false: Rex is mean. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Rex is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses.",
        "response_3": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Rex is tumpus. Tumpuses are brimpuses. Rex is brimpus. Brimpuses are mean."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are fast. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is tumpus. True or false: Fae is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is lorpus. Lorpuses are fast. Fae is fast. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are fast. Zumpus is impus. Fae is tumpus. True or false: Fae is fast. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Fae is tumpus.",
        "response_2": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Fae is tumpus. Tumpuses are lorpuses. Fae is lorpus. Lorpuses are fast."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorpuses are opaque. Dumpuses are lorpuses. Max is dumpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are opaque. Max is opaque. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Lorpuses are opaque. Impus is rompus. Max is dumpus. True or false: Max is opaque. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Max is dumpus.",
        "response_2": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are lorpuses.",
        "response_3": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus.",
        "response_4": "Max is dumpus. Dumpuses are lorpuses. Max is lorpus. Lorpuses are opaque."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpuses are fruity. Lorpus is brimpus. Stella is lorpus. True or false: Stella is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are fruity. Stella is fruity. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpuses are fruity. Jompus is rompus. Stella is lorpus. True or false: Stella is fruity. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is lorpus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is lorpus. Lorpus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpuses are fruity."
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brimpus is slow. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "answer": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is slow. Stella is slow. True",
        "noise_prompt": "Brimpus is slow. Lorpus is sterpus. Stella is jompus. True or false: Stella is slow. Let us think step by step.",
        "response_0": "",
        "response_1": "Stella is jompus.",
        "response_2": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus.",
        "response_3": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus.",
        "response_4": "Stella is jompus. Jompus is brimpus. Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is slow."
    }
]